{"tossups": [{"question": "A group of New World settlers who belonged to this group traded with the Timucuans [[tim-OO-kyoo-uns]] and were led by Jean Ribault [[ree-BOH]]. A settlement established by this group under Rene Goulaine de Laudonniere [[goo-LEHN duh loh-doh-NYEHR]] was attacked by Spanish troops under Pedro Menendez de Aviles. That settlement built by these was Fort Caroline and was built near modern-day Jacksonville, Florida. Participants in an exodus to the Americas, for ten points, who were these French Protestants?", "answer": "<b><u>Huguenot</u></b>s (accept <b><u>French Protestant</u></b>s before mentioned; prompt on <b><u>French</u></b> or <b><u>Protestant</u></b>s alone)", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {"question": "With Pierce Butler, a delegate from this family proposed that fugitive slaves should be \"delivered up like criminals\" in introducing the Fugitive Slave Clause. A man from this family negotiated the Treaty of San Lorenzo along with Manuel de Godoy in establishing the U.S. boundary with Spanish Florida. A man from this family was the Federalist Party candidate in 1804 and 1808, after which he served as president-general of the Society of the Cincinnati. For ten points, name this South Carolina family which included Charles and Charles Cotesworth.", "answer": "<b><u>Pinckney</u></b> (accept Charles <b><u>Pinckney</u></b>; accept Charles Cotesworth <b><u>Pinckney</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {"question": "During the 30 years he spent in Cochabamba, this advisor may have assisted in the Cocaine Coup. This man was hired to assist the Bolivian government deal with its opponents. This man oversaw the Rue Sainte-Catherine Roundup, which resulted in a number of his targets being sent to the Drancy internment camp. The resistance leader Jean Moulin [[moo-LAHN]] was killed by this man, who was the subject of a documentary titled <em>Hotel Terminus</em>. For ten points, name this member of the Gestapo whose actions in France led to his nickname, the \u201cButcher of Lyon.\u201d [[lee-OHN]]", "answer": "Nikolaus \u201cKlaus\u201d <b><u>Barbie</u></b> (prompt on the \"Butcher of Lyon\" before mentioned)", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {"question": "Simon Kamonyai switched his armor for this man's distinct armor set prior to the Battle of Hermannstadt, leading to Kamonyai's death after he was mistaken for this man. From the Taborites, this military leader adopted the \"Wagon Fort\" tactic he learned while serving Holy Roman Emperor Sigismund in Prague. With Ladislaus III of Poland, this general undertook the Varna Crusade of the 1440s, which failed to halt Ottoman expansion in the Balkans. The father of Mattias Corvinus was, for ten points, what Hungarian general and regent of the 15th century?", "answer": "John <b><u>Hunyadi</u></b> (or <b><u>Hunyadi</u></b> Janos; or <b><u>Sibinjanin</u></b> Janko; or Ioan de <b><u>Hunedoara</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {"question": "Edward Trumbull designed a mural on the ceiling of this building\u2019s interior that celebrates \u201chuman endeavor.\u201d Another building\u2019s designer, John J. Raskob, suspected that a spire might have been hidden to provide this building with extra height. In 1961, an effort was made to polish the steel portions of this building, including the ornamental, Gothic-inspired gargoyles on its exterior. For ten points, name this building, briefly the tallest in the world, an Art Deco skyscraper named for a car manufacturer.", "answer": "<b><u>Chrysler</u></b> Building", "metadata": "Fine Arts - Other Fine Arts - Architecture"}, {"question": "The Buddhist state of Ma-i-may have either been based on this island's city of Bay, or on a neighboring island to the southwest. In the early twentieth century, the U.S. military established bases near Angeles City and Subic Bay on this island. The USS <em>Ommaney Bay</em> sunk during a battle named for this island. Invaded by the Imperial Japanese Army in 1942, approximately 75,000 troops were forced to make a 65-mile march to prison camps on this island that same year. The Bataan Death March and the Battle of Manila occurred on, for ten points, what largest island in the Philippines?", "answer": "<b><u>Luzon</u></b> (accept Battle of <b><u>Luzon</u></b>; prompt on the \"Philippines\" before mentioned)", "metadata": "History - World History"}, {"question": "This senator\u2019s opposition to the \"Build Back Better\" Act led to a confrontation in a bathroom with activists from the group, Living United for Change. During a tight senatorial race, opponent Martha McSally claimed this politician said it was \"OK to commit treason\" after she supported Afghani-Americans joining the Taliban. This woman brought a piece of cake to the Senate chamber to accompany her \"down\" vote of Bernie Sanders's proposal to raise the federal minimum wage to fifteen dollars. For ten points, name this first openly bisexual representative in Congress, a politician from Arizona.", "answer": "Kyrsten <b><u>Sinema</u></b> (or Kyrsten Lee <b><u>Sinema</u></b>)", "metadata": "Current Events - Current Events"}, {"question": "A novel focusing on a character who works in this profession prompted James Douglas to claim that he would rather give \u201cprussic acid\u201d to a child then have them read it. Radclyffe Hall wrote that work centered on a unit in this profession which was a subject of an obscenity trial and was titled <em>The Well of Loneliness</em>. A novel focusing on a \u201ctenente\u201d [[teh-NEHN-teh]] who serves in this profession features a controversial depiction of the Battle of Caporetto. That novel focuses on Frederic Henry\u2019s experiences in this profession during World War One. For ten points, name these medical transportation workers.", "answer": "<b><u>Ambulance Driver</u></b>s (accept equivalents; prompt on \u201cmedical workers\u201d before \"medical\"; do not accept or prompt on \u201cdoctors\u201d or \u201cnurses\u201d)", "metadata": "Literature - American Literature - Misc Literature"}, {"question": "Following this war, the hill people known as the Atavika remained unconquered despite the region's annexation. During this war, one ruler resigned to using the principle of \"peaceful conquest\" known as <em>Dharmavijaya</em>, to incorporate conquered people into his empire. Following this war, a son of Chandragupta committed himself to <em>ahimsa</em>, or non-violence, for the remainder of his life according to Rock Edict number 13. Ashoka's conversion to Buddhism followed the brutality of, for ten points, what war named for a Southeast Indian kingdom?", "answer": "<b><u>Kalinga</u></b> War", "metadata": "History - World History"}, {"question": "This man allegedly bullied Philip the Handsome of Burgundy into a trade agreement so favorable to his country it was dubbed the \"Evil Agreement\" by the Dutch. Francis Lovell and Humphrey Stafford led a revolt against this monarch, but they were stopped due to the intervention of the knight John Savage. This man ruled through a group of counselors and judges known as the Star Chamber. After a consequential battle, this man married Elizabeth of York to cement his control over England. The victor of the Battle of Bosworth Field was, for ten points, what first Tudor king of England?", "answer": "<b><u>Henry VII</u></b> (prompt on \"Henry Tudor\")", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {"question": "A dish that is similar to the European <em>czernina</em> supposedly originated in this city after a man holding the blood of one animal accidentally dropped vermicelli [[vehr-mee-CHE-lee]] in the bowl. An imperial decree to solve a noise problem by killing all of this city\u2019s roosters allegedly led to the origin of one of its central dishes. This city's namesake \u201csalted duck\u201d may have originated under the aforementioned Hongwu Emperor. For ten points, name this city whose culinary tradition developed while it served as the Southern capital of the Ming Dynasty.", "answer": "<b><u>Nanjing</u></b> (accept <b><u>Nanking</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - World History"}, {}, {"question": "The \u201cGarden Suburb\u201d advised this prime minister, who claimed that one general had \u201cproved himself to be a Man.\" After a meeting with Berthier de Sauvigny [[soh-veen-YEE]], this man determined to make that general, Robert Nivelle, the commander of his own countryman, Douglas Haig. A proposal to levy land taxes on the wealthy was introduced in this man\u2019s \"People\u2019s Budget\" which was presented the decade before he led his country through a war that included the Battle of Verdun. For ten points, name this World War One British prime minister, a member of the Big Three at Versailles.", "answer": "David <b><u>Lloyd George</u></b> (accept 1st Earl <b><u>Lloyd-George</u></b> of Dwyfor; prompt on partial answer)", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {}, {"question": "This man's regime launched the Agroville program, which aimed to move demobilized soldiers and ethnic minorities to remote areas of his nation in an effort to dissuade communist infiltration. Using an underground passage to the Cha Tam Catholic Church, this man temporarily evaded a coup launched by generals of the ARVN supported by the CIA. Monk Th\u00edch Qu\u1ea3ng \u0110\u1ee9c [[THIK KWAHN DOOK]] lit himself on fire in protest of this man's regime having persecuted the Buddhist faith. The politics of South Vietnam were dominated by, for ten points, which dictator, overthrown in a 1963 coup?", "answer": "Ngo Dinh <b><u>Diem</u></b> [[NGOH-DEEN-YEERM]] (accept <b><u>Ngo</u></b> or <b><u>Ngo Dinh</u></b>; be very lenient on pronunciation, including accepting clearly phonetically correct pronunciations)  Accords named for which Swiss city partitioned French Indochina, including the creation of South and North Vietnam?  ANSWER: <b><u>Geneva</u></b> (accept <b><u>Geneva</u></b> Accords; accept <b><u>Gen\u00e8ve</u></b>; or <b><u>Genf</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - World History"}, {"question": "A variation of this experiment by Mary Cover Jones used milk and cookies as incentives. The subject of this experiment, Douglas Merritte, was revealed to have had suffered from hydrocephalus [[hy-droh-SEH-fah-luss]]. A graduate student, Rosalie Rayner, helped conduct this experiment. A caption of a photo taken during this experiment reads, \u201cNow he fears even Santa Claus.\u201d For ten points, what experiment, conducted by John B. Watson, used classical conditioning to create a phobia in a baby?", "answer": "<b><u>Little Albert</u></b> Experiment (prompt on descriptive answers)", "metadata": "Social Science - Social Science - Psychology"}, {}, {"question": "This character once convinced a Benedictine priest to steal a set of vessels to finance a supposed escape to a new life elsewhere. The surnames Clarick and Backson are part of aliases taken by this character whose son, Mordaunt, is employed by Oliver Cromwell in the novel <em>Twenty Years After</em>. This character is tasked with seducing a lover of Queen Anne, the Duke of Buckingham. Serving as a spy for Cardinal Richelieu [[reesh-LOO]], this character is later revealed to be the wife of Athos, the companion of Porthos and Aramis. For ten points, name this woman who appears in <em>The Three Musketeers</em>.", "answer": "<b><u>Milady</u><u>de Winter</u></b> (accept either underlined portion)", "metadata": "Literature - European Literature - Long Fiction"}, {}, {"question": "The pronounced size of the cartridge pouches used by members of this unit led Russians to refer to them as \u201cleatherbellies.\u201d A wooden hand that belonged to one of this group's commanders is an honored relic of this unit. The Army of Africa included this unit, which often fought alongside the <em>zouaves</em> [[ZWAHV]]. Six \u201cnational battalions\u201d once comprised this group, including one entirely of Poles. Participating in its country\u2019s colonization efforts in Algeria, this unit's members are provided with honorary citizenship.  For ten points, name this storied French military unit which allows expatriates to join.", "answer": "French <b><u>Foreign Legion</u></b> (accept <b><u>L\u00e9gion \u00e9trang\u00e8re</u></b>; or <b><u>FFL</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {}, {"question": "Holmes Colbert helped write the constitution of this tribe, whose language inspired the name of William Faulkner\u2019s Yoknapatawpha [[yok-nah-pah-TAW-fah]] County. A member of Billy the Kid\u2019s gang, named Fred Waite, was born in this tribe\u2019s \u201cNation.\u201d The <em>Impsaktea</em> and the <em>Intcutwalipa</em> [[eent-koot-wah-LEE-pah]] are two divisions of this tribe, which signed the 1818 Treaty of Tuscaloosa, contributing to Jackson\u2019s Purchase. Along with the Seminoles, Creek, Cherokee and Choctaw, this group that contemporary whites called the \"Five Civilized Tribes.\" For ten points, name this tribe of the Southeast Woodlands.", "answer": "<b><u>Chickasaw</u></b> (accept <b><u>Chikashsha</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {}, {"question": "Turkish slaves were used in a 17th century example of these ancient events to coincide with the arrival of Anne of Denmark to Britain. Frontinus records that an aqueduct traversing the so-called \"8th Hill of Rome,\" Janiculan, was specially built by Augustus to facilitate these events while also watering neighboring gardens. A dug-out basin near the Tiber hosted the first recorded iteration of these events following Julius Caesar's Quadruple Triumph. Ancient historians have confirmed that the Colosseum hosted, for ten points, what mock naval battles for entertainment?", "answer": "<em><b><u>Naumachia</u></b></em> [[now-MAH-kee-ah]] (accept <em><b><u>Naumachiae</u></b></em>; prompt on descriptions which include the word \"Mock Naval Battles\" or \"Coliseum Naval Battles\" before the final sentence)", "metadata": "History - Ancient History"}, {}, {"question": "This conflict\u2019s immediate cause was the stabbing of a sheriff by Two Stickney. A 24-year old governor named Stevens Mason led one side during this conflict. A task that William Harris was given by Edward Tiffin was a key precursor to this conflict, during which a compromise was reached via the Frostbitten Convention. Desire for access to premium soil was a key cause of this conflict, in which a nearly 500-square mile strip of land and the Upper Peninsula were given to the respective parties. For ten points, name this conflict between Ohio and Michigan.", "answer": "<b><u>Toledo</u></b> War (accept <b><u>Michigan-Ohio</u></b> War before mentioned; accept synonyms for \"War\" such as \"Conflict\" or \"Dispute\"; accept states in either order)", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {}, {"question": "One event in this country led to a nineteen-year prison sentence being given to the CEO of Odebrecht, a company that is now known as Novonor. A billionaire born in this country later moved to Singapore, possibly to avoid taxes. While at Harvard, that man from this country, Eduardo Saverin [[SAV-uh-rin]], co-founded Facebook. Corruption amongst dealers associated with this country's state-owned oil company contributed to the impeachment of Dilma Rousseff. Operation Car Wash affected Petrobras in, for ten points, what large South American country?", "answer": "Federative Republic of <b><u>Brazil</u></b> (accept Republica Federativa do <b><u>Brasil</u></b>)", "metadata": "Current Events - Current Events"}, {}, {"question": "<b><u>The HMCS</u> </b><em><b><u>Stone Frigate</u></b></em><b><u> was constructed following this treaty, which allowed</u></b> <b><u>for the Coast Guard's installation of machine guns on eleven small cutters following</u></b> <b><u>the 9/11 attacks. This treaty allowed for two (+)</u> vessels \"not exceeding the like burden each, and armed with like force\" to be positioned on certain bodies of water. This treaty stipulated that the U.S. and British North America could each maintain one military vessel and one cannon on Lakes (*) </b>Champlain and Ontario. For ten points, name this 1818 treaty that demilitarized the Great Lakes.", "answer": "<b><u>Rush-Bagot</u></b> Treaty (accept <b><u>Rush\u2013Bagot</u></b> Disarmament)", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {"question": "<b><u>One man with this name, who was given the epithet \u201cthe Hunter,\u201d was the</u></b> <b><u>subject of an effort depicted in an Ilya Repin painting featuring a reply to that man\u2019s</u></b> <b><u>demands being drafted by a group of Zaporizhian Cossacks. The first ruler of this</u></b> <b><u>name brought an end to the Interregnum, resulting in him being called the (+)</u></b> <b>\u201cRestorer.\u201d The second ruler of this name towed a series of ships along Galata in order to circumvent a chain along the Golden Horn. That man of this name was best known for a campaign completed in (*) </b>1453. For ten points, give this name of the Ottoman sultan who captured Constantinople.", "answer": "<b><u>Mehmed</u></b> (accept <b><u>Mehmed</u></b> the Hunter; or <b><u>Mehmed</u></b> IV; or Avci <b><u>Mehmed</u></b>; or <b><u>Mehmed</u></b> \u00c7elebi; or <b><u>Mehmed</u></b> I; or <b><u>Mehmed</u></b> the Restorer; or <b><u>Mehmed</u></b> Kiri\u015f\u00e7i; or <b><u>Mehmed</u> </b>Kyritzis; or <b><u>Mehmed</u></b> the Conqueror; or <b><u>Mehmed</u></b> II; or Fatih Sultan <b><u>Mehmed</u></b>; or <b><u>Me\u1e25med</u></b>-i s\u0331\u0101n\u012b; accept <b><u>Mehmet</u></b> in place of <b><u>Mehmed</u></b> in all answer lines; prompt on \"Muhammad\" or other variations)", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {"question": "<b><u>This politician was the last to be buried in the Kremlin Wall Necropolis. This</u></b> <b><u>politician's rise to his highest post allegedly occurred after he was cited as an</u></b> <b><u>\u201cagreeable guy\u201d by Andrei Gromyko. This man\u2019s government claimed that</u></b> <b><u>\u201cchauvinistic (+)</u> sentiments\u2026being whipped up in the United States\u201d contributed to his decision to boycott the 1984 Los Angeles Summer Olympics. This successor to Yuri Andropov (*) </b>was himself succeeded by a proponent of <em>glasnost</em>. For ten points, name this man who led the Soviet Union briefly before Mikhail Gorbachev.", "answer": "Konstantin <b><u>Chernenko</u></b> (or Konstantin Ustinovich <b><u>Chernenko</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {"question": "<b><u>The \u201cDon\u2019ts and Be Carefuls\u201d of these rules were sometimes referred to as the</u></b> <b><u>\u201cMagna Carta\u201d by the association that enforced it. \u201cRevenge in modern times shall not</u></b> <b><u>be justified\u201d and \u201cThe use of the Flag shall be consistently (+)</u> respectful\u201d were some of the rules in this code. The success of films such as </b><em><b>Some Like It Hot</b></em><b> (*) </b>was a leading reason this \"Code\" became irrelevant. For ten points, what \"Code\" of censorship guidelines regulated the movie industry in the United States from 1934 to 1968?", "answer": "<b><u>Hays</u></b> Code (or the Motion Picture <b><u>Production</u></b> Code)", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {"question": "<b><u>The son of a leader of this kingdom studied abroad in Europe before becoming</u></b> <b><u>bishop of Utica [[YOO-tih-kah]]. The Imbangala people produced a group of Jaga</u></b> <b><u>warriors who attacked this kingdom. That group lived south of the Kwanza (+)</u> River, which was an important waterway for this kingdom. Raffia cloth was extensively produced in this kingdom, whose leaders included a Catholic ruler who expressed discontent with the policies of Manuel I of Portugal, Afonso (*) </b>For ten points, name this African kingdom from what is today Northern Angola.", "answer": "Kingdom of <b><u>Kongo</u></b> (accept <b><u>Kongo</u></b> dya Ntotila; or Wene wa <b><u>Kongo</u></b>; or Reino do <b><u>Congo</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - World History"}, {"question": "<b><u>Much of the originally-captured footage of this phenomenon was burned on</u></b> <b><u>orders from Yevgeny Krinov in an attempt to rid his library of any flammable</u></b> <b><u>nitrates. One hypothesis claims this event formed Lake Cheko, a tiny freshwater body</u></b> <b><u>into which the river Kunyu (+)</u> empties. With Nikolay Fedorov, the mineralogist Leonid Kulik led an expedition to study this event which included extensive interviews with Evenki natives who witnessed this phenomenon. A (*) </b>Siberian river names, for ten points, what 1908 \"explosion\" possibly caused by the fracturing of an asteroid, the largest impact in recorded history?", "answer": "<b><u>Tunguska</u></b> Event (accept <b><u>Tunguska</u></b> Explosion; accept descriptors for the event at <b><u>Tunguska</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - World History"}, {"question": "<b><u>Angela Ballara [[bah-LAH-rah]] argued that the use of the common term</u></b> <b><u>describing these conflicts was misleading since they were a continuation of existing</u></b> <b><u>tribal practices. The Bay of Plenty was targeted during these conflicts, which</u></b> <b><u>prompted changes to</u> </b><em><b><u>pa</u></b></em><b><u> fortifications. The Battle of (+)</u> Moremonui [[moh-reh-moh-NOO-ee]] occurred during these conflicts, in which </b><em><b>iwi</b></em><b> raids were conducted in Waikato. Hongi Hika led one side during these conflicts, which preceded the Treaty of (*) </b>Waitangi. For ten points, name these conflicts involving the use of a namesake European armament used by the Maori.", "answer": "<b><u>Musket</u></b> Wars", "metadata": "History - World History"}, {"question": "<b><u>Know-Nothing Anson Burlingame was challenged by this man to a duel on the</u></b> <b><u>Canadian side of Niagara Falls, but this politician dropped out due to Burlingame's</u></b> <b><u>reputation as a marksman. J.L. Magee depicts this man as a villain in a political</u></b> <b><u>cartoon with the words \"Southern Chivalry Argument (+)</u> versus Clubs.\" This man was angered by a speech which attacked his first cousin once removed, Senator Andrew Butler, who was compared to Don Quixote for supporting (*) </b>slavery. An anti-slavery speech by Charles Sumner led to, for ten points, which U.S. representative caning him on the Senate floor?", "answer": "Preston <b><u>Brooks</u></b> (or Preston Smith <b><u>Brooks</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {"question": "<b><u>Members of this organization, Rafael Ramos and Wenjian Liu, were killed in</u></b> <b><u>2014 by a man who was outraged at the release of Daniel Pantaleo. The Knapp</u></b> <b><u>Commission was created to investigate this organization, several of whose members</u></b> <b><u>approached a man thought to have been selling (+)</u> cigarettes lacking tax stamps. That man, Eric Garner, was put into a chokehold by members of this organization whose highest-ranking women have included Juanita Holmes and (*) </b>Keechant Sewell. For ten points, name this law enforcement agency operating in boroughs including Manhattan.", "answer": "City of <b><u>N</u></b>ew <b><u>Y</u></b>ork <b><u>P</u></b>olice <b><u>D</u></b>epartment (or <b><u>NYPD</u></b>)", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {"question": "<b><u>The orator of this speech claimed, \u201cNever has a lawyer had to practice his</u></b> <b><u>profession under such difficult conditions.\u201d This speech asks, \u201cWhat law and what</u></b> <b><u>justice?\u201d and notes that its speaker has been held in solitary confinement for a period</u></b> <b><u>of 76 days. Delivered (+)</u> in 1953, this oration's speaker was a member of the Orthodox Party and was charged for his part in a raid on the Moncada Barracks in an attempt to overthrow Fulgencio (*) </b>Batista. For ten points, name this speech by Fidel Castro claiming that future generations would forgive him.", "answer": "<b><u>History Will Absolve Me</u></b> speech (or La <b><u>historia me absolver\u00e1</u></b>; accept \"<b><u>History</u></b> <b><u>will definitely tell it all</u></b>\"; or \"<b><u>historia definitivamente va a revelar todo</u></b>\"; prompt on descriptions of Castro's 1953 speech)", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {"question": "<b><u>One holder of this position was allegedly able to summon a butterfly from his</u></b> <b><u>palm by opening and closing it, a power supposedly given to Peter de Roches [[deh-</u><u>ROHSH]] by King Arthur. Following the death of one of these people named Hubert</u></b> <b><u>Walter, (+)</u> a dispute arose as to the succession of that position of this type in 1205. Stephen Langton struggled to seek a position of this type, leading to King John\u2019s excommunication by (*) </b>Innocent III. For ten points, name this religious position, a particularly powerful holder of whom was based in Canterbury.", "answer": "Arch<b><u>bishop</u></b>ric (accept Arch<b><u>bishop</u></b> of Canterbury; accept <b><u>Bishop</u></b> of Winchester; accept word forms)", "metadata": "History - European History"}, {}, {"question": "<b><u>This president endorsed the bipartisan Sheppard-Towner Act, which</u></b> <b><u>effectively decreased infant mortality in rural areas. Following Eugene Debs' run for</u></b> <b><u>president from prison, this man commuted his sentence along with other people</u></b> <b><u>imprisoned by the Sedition (+)</u> Act. According to multiple witnesses, whiskey confiscated by a U.S. Attorney General was served at a White House dinner by this man's wife, Florence. A heart (*) </b>attack led to the death of, for ten points, which Ohio-born president who was succeeded by his vice president, Calvin Coolidge?", "answer": "Warren G(amamliel) <b><u>Harding</u></b>", "metadata": "History - American History"}, {}], "bonuses": []}